crowfall.com 2017-09-04

# Crowfall - Throne War MMO | Privacy Policy 1.1

## Version: 1.1 - Last Modified on August 12th, 2015

**_Our Privacy Commitment_**

Art+Craft Entertainment, Inc. (" ** _Company_** ," " ** _we_** ," " ** _us_** " or " **_our_** ") is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of the Company website where this Privacy Policy is posted (individually and collectively, the " ** _Site_** ") (we refer to the Site and the services made available through the Site, collectively, as the " ** _Company Features_** "). As such, we have established and implemented this Privacy Policy to inform users of the Company Features how we use and protect the information we collect through the Site and the Company Features. By accessing the Site or using any of the Company Features, you consent to Company's collection, use, storage, deletion and disclosure of information relating to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date set forth above and is only applicable to the Site and not to any other website that you may be able to access from the Site which may have its own data collection and use practices and policies.

This policy answers the following questions:

  * What information do we collect about you and how do we use it?
  * Will we share your personal information with third parties?
  * What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?
  * What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?

**_What information do we collect about you and how do we use it?_**

**Types of Information We Collect**

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact you. You do not need to submit personal information to access certain areas of the Site, but in order to access all aspects of the Company Features, you will need to disclose personal information to us. .

We collect personal information when you create an account through the Company Features; participate in registration forms, feedback forms, order forms or surveys; receive customer or technical support and when you communicate with others through the Site, such as when you engage in our chat rooms, forums, blogs or other groups.

To create an account for the Company Features, we require you to provide certain information to create your profile, including your name, password, email address and screen name. Providing additional information beyond what is required to create an account, such as providing a photo, your age, gender, and birthdate, is entirely optional, but enables you to gain more from the Company Features. You will also have the option to add a profile picture to your account We may also collect financial qualification and billing information either directly or through a third party service provider, such as PayPal, such as billing name and address and credit/debit card information. Additionally, the Company may collect personal information submitted through online registration forms, purchase order forms or through communications with the Company.

We may also offer features of the Site that allow you to link your account to other social networking sites, such as Facebook and Twitter. If you sign up for one of these services, we may also collect personally identifiable information from these Internet sources and database services.

Through the Company Features, you may be able to link to technology, software and services owned and controlled by third parties (the " **_Third Party Features_** "). For example, we may use a third party payment providers to collect billing information for payments for purchases made by you. You may be permitted or required to submit personal information to access Third Party Features. Such use of Third Party Features and submission of information through Third Party Features will be subject to such applicable third party's terms of use, terms of service and/or privacy policy. You agree to look solely to the applicable third party and not to the Company to enforce your rights in relation thereto.

By submitting personal information through the Site, you authorize the Company to share this personal information for the purposes identified herein and on the Site, such as responding to user inquiries and processing transactions.

**_How We Use Your Personal Information_**

The personal information you provide to us will allow us to alert you of new products or services, features, or enhancements; handle your customer service questions or issues; provide for order processing; request feedback; distribute newsletters; and notify you of promotions, contests, surveys updates, or special offers that we think may interest you. We may also use your email address, phone number and postal address as part of the Company Features in sending you messages about the Company Features and other general announcements. Aditionally, personal information, such as your photo (should you choose to upload one), will be viewable by other users of the Site. Our automated systems analyze your content (including emails) to provide you personally relevant service, such as resolving customer service tickets.

We keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your activity within the Company Features. We may use personal information that you provide to us to send messages to you in response to your request to perform an activity in connection with your use of any of the Company Features and to contact you when necessary.

**Cookies**

"Cookies" are small bits of electronic information that a website sends to a visitor's browser and are stored on the visitor's hard drive. We may employ cookies in certain areas of the Site to allow us to provide information to make your online experience more convenient. For example, cookies may be used to keep track of shopping cart information, your login name and password, and your click stream data. While the Company may use cookies to track your visit to the Site, this information does not identify you personally and you remain anonymous, even if you have previously submitted personal information to the Company through the Site or otherwise. Third parties whose websites are accessible through links on the Site may also use their own cookies when you link to their site or service. The Company does not control these third parties' use of cookies and cannot guarantee that they will uphold the same privacy standards as the Company. The Company expressly disclaims any and all liability related to the collection, use or disclosure of information by third parties. You should review the privacy policies of any third party sites that you visit through a link from the Site to understand how these third parties use cookies and the information they collect through cookies. Most cookies are "session cookies" which means that they are automatically deleted at the end of each session. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you a chance to decide whether or not to accept it.

**Do Not Track**

In compliance with California legislation, AB370, effective January 1, 2014, the Company's practices in responding to "do not track signals and collecting user information over time and across a network of websites when you visit the Site are described below. We honor the request of "do not track" signals sent by your browser when you visit the Site. Additionally, the Company does not collect user information about your online activities over time and across different websites, or authorize third parties to do so.

**Google Analytics**

The Site uses Google Analytics to help us learn about who visits the Site and what pages are being viewed.

**Log Information**

Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit the Site. This information includes your Internet Protocol address, your browser type and version, the search engine you used to find the Company Features, if any, which Company Features you use and from where, and when and how long you use them. We use this information to monitor and analyze how users use the Company Features, to provide customer service and to maintain and improve the Company Features. We may also collect similar information from emails we may send to you which then help us track which emails are opened and which links are clicked by recipients. The information allows for more accurate reporting and improvement of the Company Features.

Children's Privacy

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. We take children's privacy seriously, and encourage parents to play an active role in their children's online experience at all times.

**_Will we share your personal information with third parties?_**

Sharing of Information

Except as set forth in this section, or unless we have your consent, we will not share your personal information with any person or entity other than those affiliated with the Company, entities acting on behalf of the Company and relevant third parties needed to complete a transaction, collect and maintain our information collection servers, and perform technology and related services. We use your personal information to respond to your requests and send communications to you about promotions, updates, or special offers (which may be offered by the Company or one of its business partners) that may be of interest to you. We may share your personal information with carefully selected vendors and business partners, including companies that perform marketing services and other business operations for us, under strict terms described herein. In addition, we will share the personal information we collect from you under the following circumstances:

  * _Protection of rights._ We will share personal information if we have a good faith belief that (i) access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or a request by law enforcement or governmental authorities, (ii) such action is appropriate to enforce our Terms of Use for the Company Features, including any investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) such action is necessary to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues associated with the Company Features, or (iv) such action is appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of the Company, its employees, users of the Company Features or others.
  * _Asset transfers._ If we become involved in a merger, acquisition or other transaction involving the sale of some or all of the Company's assets, user information, including personal information collected from you through your use of the Company Features, could be included in the transferred assets. Should such an event occur, we will use reasonable means to notify you through email and/or a prominent notice on the Site.
  * _Service Providers._ We may share your personal information with service providers that we engage for the purpose of marketing to you and/or processing information on our and your behalf. For example, we may partner with other companies to process payments for the Company Features. While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information. To the extent applicable, we require these entities to comply with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

**Additional Information You Should Know About Third Parties**

The Site may contain direct links to websites operated by our business partners and other third party entities. These third party websites may collect information about you when you visit them or otherwise communicate with them. This Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of third party websites linked to the Site or accessible through the Company Features. Although we encourage such third parties to adopt and follow their own privacy policies, we are not responsible for their collection and use of your personal information. You should refer to the privacy policies and statements of other websites or contact the respective webmasters of those websites to obtain information regarding their information collection, use and disclosure policies.

When you have clicked on a third party logo or URL displayed on our Site or accessible through the Company Features which links you to a different website, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the third party to see how your personal information will be handled on their website.

**_What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?_**

**Control of Your Information** You may update or delete your personal information or modify your account preferences for the Company Features by updating your profile information. However, information previously shared with other users through a chat room or through forums cannot be deleted.

**Opting Out of Receiving Communications from Us**

In the event that we send communications to you via email and you no longer want to receive our emails or other announcements, you may opt-out by using the opt-out link which is on all communications we send, emailing us at [support@artcraftent.com](mailto:support@artcraftent.com "External link") requesting opt-out and/or mailing us an unsubscribe notice to Art+Craft Entertainment, Inc. 815A Brazos St #313, Austin TX 78701 including your email address associated with your crowfall.com account. Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from us that is necessary to administer your account.

**Mediation**

If you are a resident of a country outside of the European Union, you also agree that, in the event any dispute or claim arises out of or relating to this Privacy Policy that you and the Company will attempt in good faith to negotiate a written resolution of the matter directly between the parties. If you reside in the United States, you agree that if the matter remains unresolved for forty-five (45) days after notification (via certified mail or personal delivery) that a dispute exists, all parties shall join in mediation services in Austin, Texas with a mutually agreed mediator in an attempt to resolve the dispute. Should you file any arbitration claims, or any administrative or legal actions without first having attempted to resolve the matter by mediation, then you agree that you will not be entitled to recover attorneys' fees, even if you would otherwise be entitled to them.

**Dispute Resolution for Residents of the European Union**

If you are a resident of the European Union, in the event that you have any dispute or claim arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, you may report your claim to the European Union Data Protection Authorities located in your jurisdiction.

**_What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?_**

The personal information that you provide to us is stored on servers, which are located in secured facilities and protected by protocols and procedures designed to ensure the security of such information. In addition, we restrict access to personal information to Company employees and agents who need to know this information in order to develop, operate and maintain the Company Features. All Company personnel who have access to this information are trained in the maintenance and security of such information. However, no server, computer or communications network or system, or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect user information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through the use of any of the Company Features and you acknowledge and agree that you provide such information and engage in such transmissions at your own risk. Once we receive a transmission from you, we will endeavor to maintain its security on our systems.

**_Notification of Changes_**

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time and we will post all changes on the Site.

**_Questions? Contact Us_**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [support@artcraftent.com](mailto:support@artcraftent.com).

**_Terms of Use_**

Please read the Terms of Use governing the use of the Site and the Company Features.
